{"question":"33 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1216", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2048", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2829", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6084", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1008", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1207", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"832", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3465", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1178", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3087", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3658", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1512", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2542", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1739", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4830", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"480", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1188", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6083", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2016", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1071", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2409", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1007", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1368", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2812", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"462", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1332", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1178", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1230", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2345", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"999", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"680", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1184", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1222", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3124", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"980", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1323", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4686", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4221", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3542", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"480", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1521", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2108", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2793", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"595", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2923", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2940", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"972", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4260", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1776", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5244", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1936", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3978", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1984", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5106", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1104", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"504", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4029", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2760", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2318", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2912", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4340", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4307", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1728", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4070", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1848", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"336", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2077", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"765", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3498", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1044", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3060", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1156", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4012", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"756", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3136", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1173", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1008", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3198", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4189", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2499", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2747", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1036", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"850", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3268", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1360", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1539", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"775", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4158", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1334", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"855", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3060", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1595", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1519", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2067", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1892", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1008", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2838", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1785", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"832", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3363", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"988", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4096", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2054", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"990", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"374", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2480", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3819", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1189", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2263", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1064", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2016", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"928", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5846", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1258", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2035", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"999", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3404", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2793", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2088", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1034", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3332", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1624", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1505", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2516", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"390", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3339", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1908", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"779", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1980", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2574", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"816", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1140", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1748", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1598", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1185", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5082", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2664", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1007", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2291", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2090", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3723", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3042", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4736", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3630", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"578", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"930", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1296", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2211", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"595", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2553", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"598", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2340", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1220", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2706", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4015", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1794", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1360", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1392", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1554", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2070", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1908", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3504", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1426", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4544", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2703", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2409", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1104", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3384", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"798", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1196", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3072", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2714", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1738", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1680", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5460", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"624", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1121", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"954", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2277", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2684", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4392", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1666", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1128", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1980", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1769", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1802", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4624", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4453", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3528", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3168", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2028", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2275", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1836", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"552", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1540", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1136", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1590", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6006", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2048", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3212", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2888", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2530", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4958", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5254", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2340", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1518", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"768", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2432", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5846", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2310", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2925", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3782", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"988", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3416", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4453", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4446", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1620", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2553", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1710", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"966", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1862", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1008", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4071", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1872", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1950", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5920", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"750", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"885", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3528", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3538", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1710", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1728", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4544", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1100", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2418", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2030", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"442", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2820", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2132", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1666", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1311", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3060", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1633", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"544", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4526", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"528", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2961", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"714", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1598", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5396", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"528", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"460", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1495", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3416", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4030", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2444", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4070", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1848", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1128", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1836", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1045", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1517", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3816", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1044", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1530", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1488", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4697", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3168", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2107", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2211", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1178", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4940", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1984", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1501", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"731", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2907", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3234", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1020", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2108", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3685", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1645", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"915", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1920", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5135", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1833", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1216", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1139", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3136", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2178", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3942", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2128", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3456", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2385", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2340", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2679", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2340", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"644", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2968", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2835", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2528", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1606", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4026", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1159", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2940", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2926", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4331", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2928", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1296", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3648", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"910", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4161", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1295", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5037", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3776", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"752", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1014", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3871", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2112", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1771", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1665", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4278", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3233", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3192", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1020", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5313", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5775", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2024", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2964", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3240", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4582", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1196", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"368", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4081", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3712", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2622", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"897", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1431", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4884", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1596", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2847", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4964", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1927", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"935", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2112", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1728", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6006", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2907", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3906", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5254", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5226", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"255", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4503", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1102", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5925", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"546", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1932", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1326", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2850", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3060", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1290", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2553", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3572", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3752", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1798", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4424", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1428", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1334", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3536", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5106", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2010", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1768", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"999", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1460", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"330", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2236", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6083", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4030", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3700", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4307", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2291", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2886", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4526", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"731", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2592", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"972", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3477", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1428", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"861", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3072", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"950", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3465", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"468", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1748", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"893", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1750", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1421", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1704", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1463", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1387", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5467", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1848", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"648", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1820", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1694", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2079", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1922", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5180", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4012", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3431", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1716", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2040", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3024", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1102", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1365", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2226", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1140", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2257", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2074", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3465", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2240", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1073", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"735", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"741", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"975", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"903", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1007", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2275", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"861", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3124", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5110", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1887", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1444", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1064", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2744", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1711", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3952", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4248", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1620", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2240", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2632", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4582", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1350", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2480", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4503", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4543", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"759", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2952", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2291", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1095", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"551", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3096", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"867", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"744", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1320", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1311", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1363", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4144", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3933", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1241", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3894", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2597", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2664", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2272", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"986", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23 * 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1679", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1360", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"540", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"616", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"578", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5328", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2862", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1998", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1904", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3888", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2346", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1460", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1998", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5929", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3479", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2016", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4095", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2842", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2964", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34 * 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1734", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 * 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"342", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 * 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1134", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1927", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3445", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2553", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 * 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"850", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 * 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1845", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4788", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3404", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3619", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1298", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4636", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 * 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"972", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 * 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 * 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
